there's been significant Sean in The
General insurance industry in the
financial year so far Yash gen hasn't
been tracking the story he joins in with
the main highlights well that's correct
so of course as far as the first four
months of the financial year are
concerned if one looks at the industry
the industry has managed to put a strong
growth in three of its biggest segments
which are these segments its motor
health and fire if we speak about motor
for the industry the industry is grown
at a good pace of 19 under motor as well
owned damage premium is up 17 third
party premium growing at 22 percent
health of course the growth is 24 pretty
strong in this segment retail Health up
18 Group Health up 22 and finally fire
which is up seven percent now of course
these three segments put together form
nearly 85 percent of the total business
for the industry but of course if you
read between the lines as far as the
strong growth is concerned there's a
significant churn which you also alluded
to ICICI Lombard has been a losing
Market when it comes to motor but at the
same time gaining a very strong market
share in business as far as health is
concerned so for ICICI Lombard the motor
premium just grew at about seven percent
the market share also in the first four
months was down by 116 basis points
under motor both own damage as well as
third party premium the premium growth
has been in single digit for ICICI
Lombard now let's look at Health there's
a very strong Focus from Issa Lombard in
the first four months on health the
premium is up 35 of course double digit
premium under both retail and Group
Health New India Assurance on the other
hand has focused strongly on motor of
course double digit premium up 18 in the
first four months for New India both
motor owned damage and third party
premium this gain of market share and
premium growth uh at the same time star
Health has also performed a very strong
show as far as health insurance segment
is concerned
alrightyosh thanks a lot for that so
that's about the insurance space with
that let's start